Meeting at the Miami Specialty of The White, for today's date and on our item too is notification by Director Mort Smith.
Board's campus ministry.
Mr. Steve White-South, go to power here!
I'm well at readings from the New Athletic Department
Well tough out there right now you're in a paper
You've got to be back with the members and it says ten staff members
Let us say ten staff members of all coaches
Maybe one more assistant coach
And those are the four good news today
The football office
They have 150 kids for summer school
It's a very direct, direct, direct, direct, direct.
The first year is all the world of some events
We're praying for a free-go and an awesome country
To decide to get back in you
That it's a final part
But let us pray here
Thank You for this night
Thank You For This People Who Get So Much Of A Time
And If Your Great Things Happened, You Can Have Less Delusion
Thank you everyone.
I have four public end programs,
there's a personal peer access
to the one in
The Audits which she addressed
me authority on any of
the agenda either being
not out by as
considered gender staff is
recommending item six through
nine for the percentage
and if we take them
look at those
they're
are no questions
that entertain
motion two
approve
as recommended.
Second please?
Will call
or kiss
with
Davis
I'm 10 also the associate semester service agreement or order number 20 slash 21 dash 1 for six months of general
MSU A engineering services not to exceed 60,000 combined
So this is but it's on this MSu a city council
You know all some access our City engineer
This was in continued act as our city engineer another 6 months
I'm a city manager and see if they continue on the boat soon or go for something else
Yeah, we have lots of projects. We use those to not be uptake in front
The council are getting new organizations
These streets
They do lot street that has genres
Some animals look at this channel what things want
So their very good as far as our city engineer
If i keep them further six months until you get the new city man transit
Is it just a shame amount is last time around
Well we use the so this is our six months
So you just multiply it to be 120,000
Is that what I'm using for a whole year?
Okay. This was first time when
We used your free years
It's strictly because of going through transition and
To get new city manager an opportunity
And certainly not because there are any dissatisfaction with all someone on
That i want in record
If they were gonna stay atonate
I'd be having it on free year but
You're gonna go through transition you got a new city manager
And look at them with fresh eyes and give a recommendation to the US
So one of their criticisms that we get occasionally is why are
We paying 120,000 years
To all some
It's out of high amount in our own City engineer
Can use respondent
I'd be very happy to the 120,000
Actually equates
To what we were paying for a city engineer when you
Factor them salary and fringe benefits
But would mean did have
A City Engineer
When had project
We was still hiring other engineers
So they are over seeing by
The person that hired us in
The same amount of money for the engineering
Stamp that you would get with a city engineer
Plus,
You have to depth
That organization so
Have consistency between projects
Of all different things we're working on
And
So
It's part
A lot
In particular area, but not in other areas
We're with Olson we get that full
That's exactly right
If you look at what is taking place
Right now
Now I'm about to do the waterline project on central
And then will tie into some road improvement projects
Doing a main street
The Central Avenue improvements
Will be tying it
To
The main Street program
That way you have the consistency
All of a sudden
On this project
At that time it was really tough because our former city
And general is wonderful person
But he's overstretched
We're
A little too large to
More than one engineer on board
Were two small
To be able
Really hire 1
The practical project
Rocked it or the
Excuse me,
The nickel substation redesign
They have a depth and experience to be able
To do that kind of projects
If we had us city engineer
We still would've got
Have been in the cost of engineering services
By doing this but we can increase our debt
Any other questions on
This particular item
How do I take it true?
Yes, sir.
You told me a few weeks ago
The Anderson was going to start doing some sort of business
So they're talking about that
We hired an old and designed main street
That is essential
To hire the Anderson to
Do the inspection services with regard
With our borrowing from the community
We're going to do that
And then we'll be doing the day-to–day watching
Everything is on
They will answer any questions
There's anything you can
To put in your contract or
Do what they plan and show
The State does it a lot
Having one design engineer
Then having an engineering
What are those projects?
We have to go check ourselves
Yes, we're not doing that
Which is what the State requires
So while
To know Sean and sitting here
Sean was just a face of a much larger
Deep organization
I'm always saying something bad about it
But he basically think
Of him as
Much deeper of our organizations
Any other questions?
Do we have a motion to approve item 10
Which is the Master Service agreement for six months
And second
We'll call
I
Work it
All right
Any new business
Staff reports are in
Approaching in a valuable staff's president
Question 20
Any trustee community announcements
I'm 14
The government that you do
We have a motion to adjourn
All second